# André Luiz da Silva

## Software Engineer

jobs@andresilva.cc

**%** +55 47 99900-1415

⊕ andresilva.cc

github.com/andresilva-cc

A software engineer with professional experience in web systems and mobile applications. Led and participated in the project and development of applications for public and private companies in the most diverse segments, using programming languages and tools such as JavaScript, TypeScript, Vue.js, Drupal, PHP, Laravel, Node.js, and NativeScript.

## **Experience**

#### Front-end Engineer @ Atlas Technologies

Nov 2021 - Present

#### CEO & Co-Founder @ Nuxstep

Jun 2018 - Oct 2021

- Planned and developed software projects
- Helped in the execution of IT infrastructure projects
- Helped in the daily activities of departments such as administrative, commercial, financial, support, among others
- Developed a plugin that integrates Spotify's SDK into NativeScript

#### Software Development Intern @ Gmaes Telecom

Mar 2017 - Dec 2018

- Helped in the development of a web inventory system for the City Hall of Francisco Beltrão using
  Vue.js and Laravel
- Planned, designed and developed the new website of the Federal Council of Engineering and Agronomy (CONFEA) using Drupal
- Developed an integration between the Nuvemshop e-commerce platform and SkyHub marketplace integrator
- Deployed applications on Linux and Windows servers

#### **Education**

#### UNIVALI - Universidade do Vale do Itajaí

2015 - 2019

**Bachelor of Computer Science** 

## **Technologies**

HTML **Express** CSS SQL Sass NativeScript JavaScript Flutter TypeScript Adobe XD Figma Vue.js Drupal Java PHP Shell Script Linux Laravel

Node.js Windows Server